[{"answer": "She is well", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Sacrifices.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "He is in love, and plans to be married. Hmph!", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "So whens all this supposed to happen?", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Sacrifices.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Three days, huh? Thats kinda quick", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "my friend did not even consult me before making this decision. It is obvious this girl has caused all reason to leave my friend head", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Sacrifices.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Serving eight", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "That is not what I intended. my friend has pledged to help lead the that place in the battle against the Goauld", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Sacrifices.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "my friend, this is not about you. Soon enough my friend will have to choose between his responsibility to his family and to that of his cause", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "You have no wish to fight sid", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Sacrifices.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "As you will continue to be because of your shor", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "As you will continue to be because of your shor", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Sacrifices.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "And I will not rest until all Goauld are dead.", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Can I come with you", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Sacrifices.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "There will be no union", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "That is not the point", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Sacrifices.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I know! That is why my father abandoned my mother and I", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "You still have much to learn about yoursel", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Sacrifices.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "No", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Please, return to your quarters", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Sacrifices.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Please! In time, your skills may be required, and you must be ready. Go", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I will take first watch", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Sacrifices.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "It was not a foolish promise. One day, we will all be free", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Tealc", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Sacrifices.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "One day is not soon enough", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "When the Gate opens again, aim this at your target.  The missiles will come through and strike where you aim.", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Sacrifices.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I assure you, this time it will not be necessary.", "qsentId": 26}]